illy.com 2008-11-12

# Privacy

## Our Privacy Policy

illy is committed to protecting your privacy. In order to provide you with the best information and services, and a more personalized browsing or shopping experience, we may collect information about your visit to our site.  This privacy policy explains our online information collection practices and how we use the information we collect.  The policy applies only to visitors and customers in the United States. 

**The Information We Collect  
** When you shop on our site, sign up for our mailing list or online newsletter or participate in an online forum, community or message board, we may collect certain personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. 

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our site. Examples of this type of information include the domain name of your Internet service provider and the type of browser you are using. 

**How We Use Collected Information  
** Personally identifiable information you provide may be used to fulfill your shopping order, requests for information and services and to offer you products, services, contests, surveys and information we think may be of value to you. We may also, from time to time, extend selected offers or promotional information on behalf of one of our partners, but we do not sell, rent, share or give your personally identifiable information to third parties. When you place an order through our online store, request a catalog, sign up for our mailing list or online newsletter, enter a contest or sweepstakes or join an online community, forum or message board, we will automatically add you to our list to receive special offers by email and/or mail. 

Non-personally identifiable information we collect may be used in aggregate to optimize the design of our site, enhance the user experience and provide demographic information about our users. 

We reserve the right to disclose any information without notice or consent in response to a legal request, regulation or subpoena, or where we believe it is necessary to take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud or to protect the integrity of our site or the safety of our visitors. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable you to enjoy special features and an enhanced web experience by tracking your personal preferences. If you wish to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, or be notified when a new one is received, look under the "help" menu on your browser's tool bar. Please note, however, that if you disable cookies, you will not be able to shop in our online store. 

Some of our web pages may contain small electronic images known as "web beacons" or single-pixel gifs. These images are placed on a web page to collect data such as counting the number of users who have visited the page or acted upon a promotional message. 

**Security**   
When you provide us with information or place an order, your information is kept safe and secure through encoding with SSL technology, an encryption protocol that protects information as it travels over the Internet. 

How You Can Change Your Information and Notification Preferences   
You can, at any time, update or modify your personally identifiable information and preferences regarding email, newsletter or mail. 

By e-mail: Send a request to [customer.service@illyusa.com](mailto:customer.service@illyusa.com)

By Phone: Call toll-free 877-4MY-ILLY (877-469-4559) Monday through Friday between 9:00 am and 7:00 pm E.S.T. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**   
From time to time we may update or refine this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review our policy periodically on our web site.
